表面上看来，创建一个项目列表是一件很简单的事情。
On the surface, creating a list of items is simple enough.
Android 包括 Scroll View，在这你可以使用linear布局，
Android includes a Scroll View into which you can place any
依次来安排所包含的元素，使其成为垂直列表。
linear layout that in turn arranges each item it contains into a vertical list.
注意底部已被覆盖掉linear布局的元素。
Note the items which have fallen off the bottom off the linear layout. And
因此，在UI中不可见。
therefore aren't currently visible in that UI. The Scroll View,
Scroll 视图，顾名思义，将通过它的布局的内容的用户可以滚动使用。
as the name suggests, will let the user scroll through the contents of
然而，在内存有限的设备上使用Scroll 视图是个挑战，
the layout it contains. But there's a challenge associated with that approach on
当中，触摸反应是很关键的。
a device with limited memory, and where touch responsiveness is
当你有五十个元素在列表中，
critically important. If you have 50 items in a list and
可以再任意时刻显示十个元素在屏幕上。
can fit 10 items on screen at any given time. What's the minimum number of
那么问题来了，你需要在列表中创建多少个元素才能显示屏幕的最小显示数呢？
views you'd need to create in order to scroll through every item on the list?
可能你一会儿不知道答案，多想想，
The answer might not be immediately obvious but think about ways in which you
你可以更高效的使用视图来显示整个列表。
can be more efficient in your use of the views used to display the entire list.